

Profile

I'm a passionate front-end developer with over a year of experience in the field. After completing my degree in computer science, I discovered my love for creating beautiful, functional websites and applications.

My strong problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and ability to work under tight deadlines have allowed me to consistently deliver high-quality work that meets my clients' needs. In my free time, I enjoy staying up-to-date on the latest web development trends and exploring new technologies.

Employment History

Freelance Front End Developer at Upwork, Remote

March 2022 — Present

- Top Rated Freelancer
- Working with clients on creating websites, landing pages and web applications according to requirements and designs.
- Consulting clients on making decisions about the tooling/problem solving.
- Working with different technologies as HTML/CSS/JS, as well as with frameworks like React and Vue.
- As a freelancer have to be able to make decisions on my own as well as consulting with the client about particular problem or issue
- Direct and permanent communication with clients about the requirements, feedback and code review.

Web Content Manager at Telecom Armenia, Yerevan

July 2019 — Present

- Collaborated with marketing and design teams to develop and plan site content, layout and style.
- Directed content of website by gathering information and integrating data from other departments.
- Writing technical requirements for the new CMS features
- Testing new CMS features
- Creating landing pages for the new products
- Using HTML/CSS/JavaScript to build custom components for the landing pages

Education

Bachelor's degree in Political Science, Russian Armenian University, Yerevan

September 2013 — May 2017

Graduated with Honors

Details

Yerevan

Armenia

+37495288221

vahe.abov@gmail.com

Skills

HTML & CSS

SCSS/SASS

JavaScript

Vue

React

TypeScript

NodeJS

Git

Gulp

Webpack

Figma

Adobe XD

Firebase

Links

Linkedin

Personal Website

GitHub

Upwork

Stack Overflow

Languages

English

Russian

Armenian

Master's degree in Cultural Journalism, Russian Armenian University

September 2017 — May 2019